Eddy Mbuti Wanza

Contact Information

Location: Nairobi, Kenya

Email: eddymbuti@gmail.com

Phone: +254 715053507

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/wanza-eddy-mbuti-13845977?

Education

Bachelor of Arts in Criminology and Penology

Maasai Mara University, Kenya

Completed: 2018

Summary

Content writer, creative writer, customer service specialist, digital marketing specialist, and social media management specialist with experience in freelancing and working with SEO agencies. I'm currently expanding my skills to become a Full-Stack Software Engineer, Data Analyst, and Cybersecurity Specialist - where I'll enjoy building efficient, user-friendly applications, analyzing data for meaningful insights, and ensuring digital security.

Professional Experience

Content Writer, Digital Marketer

Ian Hetch (Nov 2023 - Present)

- Editing and optimizing website content for Dumpster Enterprises and Speedy Car Shipping businesses.
- Optimizing content using Surfer SEO tool
- Writing homepage content
- Writing service page content
- Writing GMB profile content
- Rewriting and proofreading website content
- Writing email campaigns
- Setting up and scheduling emails via Mailchimp

Case Engine (2020-2023)

- Writing Press releases
- Writing neighborhood supporting articles
- Writing Point of Interest supporting articles
- Writing blog articles
- Editing and proofreading blog articles

AgencyX (2021 – 2023)

- Writing location landing pages
- Writing neighborhood supporting articles
- Writing Point of Interest supporting articles
- Writing homepage content
- Writing service page content

Skills

Strong communication and interpersonal skills

Content writing

Digital marketing and inbound marketing

Social media management and customer service

Editing and proofreading

Website optimization

Email marketing

Proficiency in social media analytics and scheduling tools

Familiarity with e-commerce platforms

Qualifications

Strong communication and interpersonal skills, with the ability to empathize and connect with individuals from diverse backgrounds

Ability to work independently and collaborate effectively with a remote team

Strong attention to detail and accuracy in data entry and management

Excellent communication and interpersonal skills

Strong problem-solving and analytical skills

Ability to prioritize and manage multiple tasks simultaneously

Willingness to learn and adapt to new technologies and processes

Availability

Flexible